- 高清精品短片分享APP 「 V电影 」-
关注微信：V电影 每日一部精彩短片
1080P：
We're born to fly
我们注定翱翔
So let's keep living till it all falls down
请勿止步
Let's close our eyes
闭上双眼
And let the moment drown the whole world out
此刻比全世界都重要
We're in this together
我们团结一心
Hear our hearts beat together!
聆听彼此共同的心跳
We stand strong together
团结一致 更加强大
We're in this forever!
此刻即是永恒
This one's for you!
这场比赛献给你
This one's for you.
Waving colored flags
挥舞彩旗
We won't surrender, there's no standing down
绝不屈服
Love's a playing field
爱是赛场
It's full of winners, we're breaking new ground
满场赢家 我们正开天辟地
We're in this together
我们团结一心
Hear our hearts beat together!
聆听彼此共同的心跳
We stand strong together
团结一致 更加强大
We're in this forever!
此刻即是永恒
This one's for you!
这场比赛献给你
This one's for you.
In this together
在一起
We're in this together
我们团结一心
Hear our hearts beat together!
聆听彼此共同的心跳
We stand strong together
团结一致 更加强大
We're in this forever!
此刻即是永恒
This one's for you
这场比赛献给你